<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Hugo Profile</title>
    <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Hugo Profile</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 19:07:25 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Online Shopping System</title>
      <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/projects/online-shopping-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 19:07:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/projects/online-shopping-system/</guid>
      <description>Lab Sup : Lab Supplies management system Overview LabSup is a Spring and Hibernate based Lab supplies management system to tracking lab supplies and manage lab staff consumption of lab supplies.
My work at a glance Built a web application based on Spring MVC to support item search and listing (dependency injection, inversion of control, REST API etc.). Implemented security workflow via in-memory and JDBC authentication provided by Spring Security. Utilized Hibernate to provide better support of database operations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starlink: React JS based Starlink Trajectory Visualization</title>
      <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/projects/starlink/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 19:07:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/projects/starlink/</guid>
      <description>Overview Starlink: React JS based Starlink Trajectory Visualization
My work at a glance Setup the Repo by leveraging the React official CLI tool, and use NPM to manage project dependencies. Design the layout, component interface and data flow before the implementation. Built forms to collect user observation geo information using Ant Design component library. Fetch nearby satellites information and position prediction data through the N2YO API(s). Animated selected satellite paths on a world map using React-Simple-Map to improve the user friendness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tin-News - an android based news app</title>
      <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/projects/android-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 19:07:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/projects/android-news/</guid>
      <description>Overview Tinnews: a Tinder-like News App
My work at a glance Designed the Instagram Flavor News app based on Google Component Architectural MVVM Pattern. Implemented the bottom bar &amp;amp; page navigation using JetPack navigation component. Utilized 3rd party CardStackView(RecyclerView) to support swipe gestures for liking/disliking the news. Built the Room Database with LiveData &amp;amp; ViewModel to support local cache and offline model. Integrated Retrofit and LiveData to pull the latest news data from a RESTFUL endpoint (newsapi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Job Finder Plus</title>
      <link>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/projects/job-recommendation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 17:35:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-profile.netlify.app/projects/job-recommendation/</guid>
      <description>Job Finder Plus Overview Job plus is a personalized job recommendation engine. It allows users to find posted nearby job from github jobs. User registration is designed to achieve personalized job recomemdation. Item based job recommendation can be made through user&amp;rsquo;s favorite job label.
My work at a glance Designed and implemented an interactive web app for users to search and apply available job positions. Performed front-end web UI design and implementation using HTML/CSS/JavaScript.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
